Dear Sir / Madam.

As you can see I have over 20 years' experience in large transformations programs leveraging TOGAF, eTOM, AGILE, SAFe and more recently DevOps_in several continents (Madrid, London, Dubai, Doha, Helsinki, Johannesburg, Manila, Beijing, Prague...) for the Telecom Industry.

As Program Director (over 17 years) I have led large transformation programs replacing or upgrading complex BSS/OSS Architectures leading large (+500) and complex teams (+10 Direct Reports) for the Telecom Industry.

I am also used to managing large budgets (USD+30M) and to engage with Cxx executives to define business objectives thus I am used to reporting at Cxx level.

These last years as transformation lead for a consulting firm I have developed solid cloud skills since all the programs have been cloud based (cloud transition or cloud native)

I have two degrees in IT engineering as well as a MBA from ESADE. I have recently finished my Data Science Course at HarvardX and I am currently taking a DevOps master at Purdue (On-line campus).

I am now looking for new challenges in my career and his role presents the type of role that is both demanding and challenging.

Si	n	^	\sim	r	\sim	١,,	
. DI		ι.	_		-	ıv	

GABRIEL LOPEZ GARCIA



Spanish Citizen. Residencie: Madrid.

gabriel.lopez.garcia@gmail.com.

Telephone: +34 699 435 147.

Business Travel. English (Fluent) – Spanish (Native)

Summary

A solid (+20 years) international career in BSS/OSS Transformation Programs for the CME (communications, media and entertainment) industry.

Over 15 years (since 2006) managing, designing, and leading large IT Transformation Programs and Transformation Program Portfolios.

Elisa. Implementation of BSSS/OSS Transformation— Helsinki.
Telkom SA. Design & Implementation of BSS/OSS Transformation. — Johannesburg. Etisalat. Design of Full BSS/OSS Transformation— Dubai.
Beijing Mobile. Audit of BSS/OSS Transformation— Beijing.
San Miguel Telekom — Greenfield Design Business and BSS/OSS — Manila.
Vodafone Qatar. Design & Implementation. Greenfield BSS/OSS - Doha. (and more).

I have a deep understanding of the architectural (TOGAF) and process (eTOM) models that support the Telco industry.

I have extensive experience working in multi-vendor programs, having led up to ten vendors in one program as prime S.I.

I have been certified by PMI, PRINCE2 and SAFe and I have held a leading role (while in Amdocs. Global Program Leadership Manager) as head of the global program management center where I was responsible for ensuring large programs followed best practices thus, I have strong Program management and leadership skills.

Professional Experience.

Jan 2018 - Present. BEAGA ASESORES.

I.T. Transformation Director.

Main Responsibilities.

I design and manage complex IT Transformation programs (either cloud native or cloud transition) for corporate clients.

Successes:

Average yearly objectives since 2018: 125%

Five ERP/BSS/OSS Successful Transformation Programs.

One full transition from Semi-Agile to DevOps.

Feb 2012- Dec 2017. Hewllet Packard. London - Dubai

Transformation Global Manager. I.T. Strategy and Transformation. CME

Main Responsibilities.

Responsible for identifying, developing, designing, and delivering transformation programs. (USD 50M - USD150M) for the CME industry (communication, entertainment and media).

Engage with clients (at executive level) and build relationships by demonstrating competency at Cxx level on technology, business processes, operations and cost management.

Program director for the largest and more complex programs.

Member of the Strategic Sales Team for Telecom and Retail. Member of the Strategic Sales Center for EMEA.

Jan 2009 – Jan 2012. Electronic Data Systems. EDS. London.

Senior Manger Consulting. IT Strategy and Transformation Practice. CME

Main Responsibilities. Reporting to the head of consulting for EMEA. Member of the CME (communication, entertainment and media) Transformation Practice.

Acting as Transformation Director for projects and portfolios with headcount over +100 and project budgets over 50M USD.

Owner of the product "I.T. Transformation" for the EMEA region. Responsible for design and coordination across all projects under that offer.

Oct 2006- Dec 2008. Amdocs Consulting Services. Tel Aviv - London

PMO Lead & Program Leadership Manager.

About Amdocs: Is an Israeli company that provides Business and Operational Support Systems for I.T. and Telecom companies.

Main Responsibilities. Reporting to the EMEA V.P of consulting.

PMO lead for large BSS/OSS transformation programs for the Telco sector.

As Program Leadership Manager responsible of ensuring strategic I.T. programs across regions (America, Europe and Asia) were properly defined properly and with a with a clear business value realization program.

Senior Consultant. IT Practice.

Main Responsibilities. Project Manager and PMO in a large OSS transformation program for Telefonica.

Program schedule, program budget, program risk management, program dependencies, program governance.

Education

ESADE. Master of Business Administration (MBA). (2004 - 2006)

UNNE. IT Engineering. Bachelor of Science Engineering. (2001 - 2003)

UNNE. Telecom System Engineering. Bachelor of Science Engineering. (1998 - 2001)

Professional Training

Data Science with Python (CS109x) - HarvardX. 2023

SAFe Software Engineering – Scaled Agile. (Renewal Exam 23/11/23)

Financia Mechanics. London. Financial Modelling. 2018.

PMI Institute. London. Project Management Professional.2007

Prince2 Institute . London. Prince2 Manager Course. 2010

ESADE. Barcelona. Agile. Scrum Master. 2009

Cisco Networking Academy. Cisco Certified Network Associate CCNA. 2003.